#### Contact

twhsn@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicole-griffin-381198b7 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Word PowerPoint

# Nicole Griffin

Registered Nurse, CCRN

Dallas, Texas

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Vital Signs, Critical Care Nursing, Time Management, and Teamwork. Strong healthcare services professional with a Bachelor's Degree focused in Nursing from Texas Christian University. Certified in devices such as LVAD, IABP, ECMO, Impella.

### Experience

Baylor University Medical Center Registered Nurse June 2016 - Present (4 years)

Dallas, Texas

Cardiothoracic surgery and Transplant ICU

Texas Health Harris Methodist Hospital Southwest Nurse Extern

May 2015 - May 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Dallas/Fort Worth Area

- · Assist patients with ADLs such as bathing, hair, dressing, mouth care
- Assist with ambulating, transfer, of patient to chair/bed/stretcher and repositioning of patient in bed
- Assist with setting up meal for patient and/or feeding patient
- · Measure and record vital signs
- Measure and record I&O
- Collect specimens
- Apply restraints when ordered
- · Discontinue short term PIV catheters
- Apply/change sterile dressing under the supervision of a RN
- Perform insertion of urinary catheters under the supervision of a RN
- Insert IV catheters under the supervision of a RN
- Insert NG tubes and check placement under the supervision of a RN

Conroe Regional Medical Center Nursing Student Intern June 2013 - July 2014 (1 year 2 months)

- •Assisted nurses on the ICU floor with NG tube placement, IV placement, foley catheter placement, and general patient care
- Assisted doctor in arterial and central line placement in the ICU
- •Assisted secretarial staff with general operations of the ICU
- •Helped transport patients to and from the Cath Lab and observed different interventions in the Cath Lab
- •Assisted with set-up in Interventional Radiology and observed different interventions
- •Worked in the Medical Staff office
- ·Sat in on bylaws meeting

#### Education

Texas Christian University
Bachelor's Degree, Nursing · (2012 - 2016)

The Woodlands High School (2008 - 2012)